<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GWeatherWatch Companion</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Status</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Setup</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="btnWhenHavePermissions">Permissions granted</string>
    <string name="btnWhenNoPermissions">Grant permissions</string>
    <string name="lbl_location">Location permissions are required for weather updates. Please grant permissions by pressing the button below. Approximate location is enough, although precise location will produce more accurate results.</string>
    <string name="lbl_location_given">Location permissions are required for weather updates. Please grant permissions by pressing the button below. Approximate location is enough, although precise location will produce more accurate results — DONE</string>
    <string name="lbl_bkgnd_location">This app requests location in the background to update the watchface. Please grant background location permission (after granting location access above).</string>
    <string name="lbl_bkgnd_location_given">This app requests location in the background to update the watchface. Please grant background location permission (after granting location access above) — DONE</string>
    <string name="lbl_error">It appears there was an error setting up permissions. Android does not allow requesting permissions multiple times. To grant permissions please either:\n- Go to app settings and grant location permissions \"all the time\"\n- Uninstall and install the app again and try pressing buttons above again.</string>
    <string name="lbl_foreground_service">This app interacts with your smartwatch, and it needs to have a connection to ConnectIQ app. Please setup the connection.</string>
    <string name="lbl_foreground_service_done">This app interacts with your smartwatch, and it needs to have a connection to ConnectIQ app. Please setup the connection — DONE</string>
    <string name="btn_service_given">Done</string>
    <string name="btn_service_not_given">Setup</string>
    <string name="lbl_last_run">Time since service last ran (should be below 1 hour).</string>
    <string name="lbl_last_send">Time since last successful data send (should be below 1 hour).</string>
    <string name="btnSendNowLabel">Send location now</string>
</resources>
